<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- Fish -->

  <VCEF_CrayfishItem.label>crayfish (adept catch)</VCEF_CrayfishItem.label>
  <VCEF_CrayfishItem.description>Raw crayfish. Crayfish are freshwater crustaceans resembling small lobsters (to which they are related). Some species are found in brooks and streams, where fresh water is running, while others thrive in swamps, ditches, and paddy fields.\n\nThis is an adept catch and provides double nutrition than other fish in their size category.</VCEF_CrayfishItem.description>

  <VCEF_ButterFishItem.label>butterfish (adept catch)</VCEF_ButterFishItem.label>
  <VCEF_ButterFishItem.description>Raw Atlantic butterfish. The Atlantic butterfish is distinguished by its very thin, deep body, resembling a flounder on edge. It earned its buttery name from its high oil content.\n\nThis is an adept catch and provides double nutrition than other fish in their size category.</VCEF_ButterFishItem.description>

  <VCEF_FreshwaterStingrayItem.label>freshwater stingray (adept catch)</VCEF_FreshwaterStingrayItem.label>
  <VCEF_FreshwaterStingrayItem.description>Raw freshwater stingray. Freshwater stingrays are one of the only rays inhabiting freshwater rather than saltwater. Though docile animals, they were responsiblein old Earth for more injuries to humans each year than any other Amazonian species.\n\nThis is an adept catch and provides double nutrition than other fish in their size category.</VCEF_FreshwaterStingrayItem.description>

  <VCEF_FlyingFishItem.label>flying fish (adept catch)</VCEF_FlyingFishItem.label>
  <VCEF_FlyingFishItem.description>Raw flying fish. While they cannot fly in the same way a bird does, flying fish can make powerful, self-propelled leaps out of the water where their long wing-like fins enable gliding for considerable distances above the water's surface.\n\nThis is an adept catch and provides double nutrition than other fish in their size category.</VCEF_FlyingFishItem.description>

  <VCEF_ArapaimaItem.label>arapaima (adept catch)</VCEF_ArapaimaItem.label>
  <VCEF_ArapaimaItem.description>Raw arapaima. On old Earth, it was among the world's largest freshwater fish, reaching as much as 3 m in length. It was an important food fish.\n\nThis is an adept catch and provides double nutrition than other fish in their size category.</VCEF_ArapaimaItem.description>

  <VCEF_ShortfinMakoSharkItem.label>shortfin mako shark (adept catch)</VCEF_ShortfinMakoSharkItem.label>
  <VCEF_ShortfinMakoSharkItem.description>Raw shortfin mako shark. A large, predatory shark that lives in the open ocean and is often considered the fastest shark. It is known for its incredible leaping ability and can be observed jumping to extreme heights (out of the water) when hunting.\n\nThis is an adept catch and provides double nutrition than other fish in their size category.</VCEF_ShortfinMakoSharkItem.description>


</LanguageData>